So have you ever seen this on any brand
face, where the branch is being talked about and after
putting some details there, disappointed
customers are copying and pasting their complaints,
they used to go to every forum and
copying and pasting incoming, have you ever
seen this, we have also seen this many times, but this
time something like this happened with us, I will tell you, the
name of the oil is Sameera, it is fine for penis
and I know all the different oil and I keep
making videos related to such side for you,
if you have not subscribed to our channel yet,
then definitely
subscribe to my channel and if there will be two things
then we will also be motivated, in English
for more videos and skimming also, you will also
remain updated with whatever financial information is there and you will also keep getting
some clarification and the
high tide is to give you happiness,
creating awareness of penis, I was talking that have
you ever seen that today's
debt customer, any deposit customer, by
going to the forum, going to the brand form and changing
his Akram plane  Presenting
something similar happened with us too, I had
made this video of Sonth on my tears, after which I had
told about myself and its constipation and everything in detail, what all buttons have
you missed or not, a lot of cyber
cafes have come to you in English on this video
and on that a gentleman came who expressed his
grievances and his disappointment and
put this complaint in front of Max Bupa,
Sonu said, good quality ma'am, poor bus,
profession in Max Bupa is very very very bad
hair day cream and always been
submitted on 30th September 2010, today the
company has not cleared the claim of
quantum 15013 spider customer, the people was
so badly in form sisters, come Babuji, let us give
you a smile on this, our support
staff is rich which already submitted on
divine deities were stopped for telling him
for the game to website for reimbursement of
maths predictions for TDS, this is the first
suggestion I read  I did not like this comment, it is not
appropriate for me to represent quite a while now, and I am
working with them, so if there is a
cricket stadium pandhari at the maximum,
then it can also happen in tuition that our
sorry policy, we have done some problem with them
too,
you felt that you should do some work on
communication, what happened, there is a problem in this, there is a
problem, I also
told them to decide the method, share your reminder,
like this to thank you, this vitamin Sonu
shared his remedy because Himanshu
had this, I had to go to the road of the problem,
Vikas, as I told you, I have been with
such a setting for many years with the CPI(M), so
my supporter of America, the fierce trust
volume maximum, I believe that the currency is
our irresponsibility because the details should
not be spoiled, there is a bill for so many years, so
why is there a problem with the approach maximum and share details, escalator, and the customer
is so detailed, then I came to know that some such cuts can be made
due to which he was
not able to go to the play music end, he was not able to reach New Zealand,
so  There was some
communication gap,
cricket was not being able to know which page he was
on, he was not able to join the line,
Darubaksh in Ubuntu followed you, that means customer was
also calling Max Bupa customer care every
time but again because he did
not have any policy as an agent advisor and
he had bought a bike,
Falguni and in the bank you know there is no after sales
service, so that policy was only
arranged from here, so he had to
follow it himself, so that professional storm was
not happening, when we went for communication, that
means a line comes out from this,
water export can only be done because he knows how the
companies press knows how the
process of that work is done, that
one point is needed, that is still as important today, those who are
intermediate
science and flat buyers, agents
from science college, their motives are still as
important as before, so if he had
positive why would he have any advisor, then he would
definitely get Tiger Hills, so
whenever any quality pass  All these
tips go there and come back to
us, then we get our response,
they should be properly educated about
which things are good and
which are not,
which is the appropriate product for them and we train them, that is,
day * know what is the element for them, what is
news and
what will be the effect of this process, it is
our objective to make the policy 100%, to maintain it later
also and a verification also keeps happening in
our belt, the same
Ashwatthama comes back to uncle, on whom
tomatoes talk from above and
shows urgency that the country also has to record immediately and on
oxygen basis they have already turned white,
now we have not got time, in the morning at Neetu's
house and what should I do here, I have maths, I take it urgently,
this letter to the highest
level and I
promise to record it as soon as possible, you got all this,
just 2 days after loading, Max
Bupa gave me the confirmation on his mobile,
so for this he  They were facing problems due to TDS, they were
talking to us from a distance but they were not able to get a solution,
they got a solution in two days,
then they came back,
they got permission from our video, from which they will get
confirmation because the camera is installed, Yadav's
video to write this message, so what do you write,
he has written that today I will send you in the
next messenger not clearing respond 150
days of including wedding validity call me yes
slide comment on YouTube
you brainly.com Paswan Pandey this was in the
mail today rolla internship,
so you open the settings, duty wonderful experience,
thank you so much, this
policy was taken to IDBI Bank, Vriddhi
health benefit research, something which
protects meeting, someone needs to
like, comment, share and
reputation, so the insurance agents are thinking
that somewhere
this position has to be grand, he has done all our and
he has done all the eating and even super
impressive and what insurance policy
through RCB's customer support
insurance policy on this same company through which
Those who were
without insurance, they will take
insurance policy from us for CPI(M) It is not just a one
time transaction, it is the only relationship Ansh will
sleep with my device
reference in future and the customer for
life vitamin reaction and help them create
Mashuka also understood the vegetable of the emergency team
in emergency and nerve and
try to entertain quickly, then the
reputation and
credibility of both of them remained precious, not only
customer retention but also he became a customer in future, that is
why I am sharing with you,
first of all I am very happy, that is why
I am adding everyone, if someone is facing a
problem, please file a complaint
on our platform, secondly we saw the problem
of Sakshi and we thought of taking action against them
and the responsibility
is to solve the problem of the vegetable, thirdly
our uterus was in Mysore and it got cemented,
sources not only under customer Veer only
from my reference, a tuition fee if you
feel that any of your films are stuck
or for any reason  I am not able to get it clear from
* With regards to life
insurance, health insurance, mutual fund,
Subedar, I dare to help you. I do
not promise whether we will be able to find your solution
or not, but we will try our best to
give you clarity as to what
goes where, morning suit or
night suit, thank you, it is so much specific but Jhal Jhal Jhal